joomlahacks.com 2014-11-22

# JoomlaHacks.com / help / privacy policy

You agree that the terms of the Privacy Policy are incorporated into these Terms Of Use as though set forth in full herein. 

#### 1\. Information Collected

It is our policy that all information provided remain confidential and not be disclosed to any other party. We have implemented security measures designed to keep all information you provide to us strictly confidential. We will not resell, rent or share the information you provide to us with any unaffiliated third party, except as required by law or, with your consent, to process or evaluate a proposed transaction. We respect your privacy and only intend to use the information you send to us in a responsible and secure manner. This pertains to information collected via application or throughout our due diligence processes. 

#### 2\. How The Information Is Used

We only use the information we collect to communicate with you, member of JoomlaHacks.com. 

#### 3\. Updating Or Deleting Information

The information you provide can be changed or deleted at any time by contacting us. 

#### 4\. Privacy Statement Changes

If this Privacy Policy ever changes, we will post a new version on this site and e-mail you a new version. We will provide you with advance notice of any such material change to the e-mail you provide to us except in circumstances where advanced written notice would not be practical. We may seek your affirmative consent to changes in the Privacy Policy for some changes; other changes will be effective unless you stop using the Services. We will clearly state in any notice of change to the Privacy Policy what change is proposed and your choices.
